A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz FA1069
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Physics Today, 1968 September (Box 75, Folder 36)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Dupont Innovation, Volume 2, Number 1, 1970 Fall (Box 75, Folder 37)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Pad, Note (Box 75, Folder 38)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Introductory Remarks, Caspary Hall, 1972 February 18 (Box 75, Folder 39)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Science Serves Society, Lee A. Dubridge, 1969 June 6 (Box 75, Folder 40)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Research: The Third Dimension, USU Bulletin 13 (Box 75, Folder 41)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - United States Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs - The Amendment to End the War, 1970 May 14 (Box 75, Folder 42)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Annual Review of Material Science, Volume 1, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 43)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Science Resources Studies, Highlights, 1970 August 11 (Box 75, Folder 44)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Program - Hunter College Centennial 1870-1970, 1970 February 11-13 (Box 75, Folder 45)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - For Action - Seitz on Technology and the Environment, 1970 January 20 (Box 75, Folder 46)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Gell-Man Report, 1970 June 16 (Box 75, Folder 47)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Western European Scientific Museums - A Survey, 1971 March (Box 75, Folder 48)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Implications of the Rejection of the Supersonic Transport, Fourth Draft, 1971 June 1 (Box 75, Folder 49)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - NAS Brochure, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 50)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - The Future of Solid-State Science, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 51)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Remarks by Seitz - Retirement Celebration of Dr. Eugene P. Wigner, "Reminiscenses", Princeton, NJ, 1971 May 1 (Box 75, Folder 52)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Topics in Modern Physics - A Tribute to Edward U. London, Forward by Seitz, 1971 September 27 (Box 75, Folder 53)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Rough Draft - Remarks, Princeton University, 1970 March 17 (Box 75, Folder 54)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Remarks, Rockeller University Commencement, The Parable of the Far-Sighted Scientist, 1970 June 12 (Box 75, Folder 55)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Science and the University, The Electrochemical Society, Reviews and News by Seitz, Volume 118, Number 10, 1971 October (Box 75, Folder 56)
- Academic Press, 1973-1993 (Box 76, Folder 1-5)
- Accademia Mediterranea Della Scienze (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Accuracy in Media, 1972-1987 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Akzo, Inc., 1992 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Air Force Office of Scientific Research, 1969-1972 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Alliance for Engineering in Medicine and Biology, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- American Academy of Achievement, 1967-1985 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- American Academy of Arts and Science, 1969-1991 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1982-1992 (Box 76, Folder 13-19)
- American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1969-1981 (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
- American Association for the Advancement of Technology (AAAT), 1989-1991 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- American Association of University Professor, 1971-1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- American Health Foundation, 1971-1988 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- American Institute of Mining, Metallurgical and Petroleum Engineers (AIME), 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- American Institute of Research, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- American Institute of Physics (AIP) - Center for History of Physics, 1981-1989 (Box 77, Folder 9-19)
- American Institute of Physics (AIP), 1976-1993 (Box 78, Folder 1-6)
- American Museum of Natural History (AMNH), 1980-1984 (Box 78, Folder 7-15)
- American Museum of Natural History (AMNH), 1984-1992 (Box 79, Folder 1-8)
- American Nuclear Energy Society, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- American Philosophical Society (APS), 1969-1993 (Box 79, Folder 10-15)
- American Philosophical Society (APS) - Benjamin Franklin Medal, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- American Philosophical Society (APS) - Joseph Henry papers, 1979-1988 (Box 80, Folder 2-4)
- Annual Review of Materials, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- The American Physical Society, 1966-1993 (Box 80, Folder 6-9)
- American Society of Mechanical Engineers - Nuclear Energy Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Argonne National Laboratory, 1969-1982 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- ASM-Tms Acta Metallurgica, 1992-1993 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Aspen Center for Physics, 1970-1972 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Atlantic Legal Foundation, 1990-1993 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Atomic Energy Commission, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Base National Advisory Board, 1983-1985 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Belgian-American Education Foundation, 1975-1976, 1988-1992 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Business Today, 1969-1974 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Carnegie Commission Workshop, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Case Western Reserve - Michelson-Morley Center Physics Symposium (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS), 1986-1993 (Box 80, Folder 21-22)
- Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS), 1980-1985 (Box 81, Folder 1-15)
- Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS), 1969-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1-7)
- Center for Strategix and International Studies (CSIS) - NATO - The Next Thirty Years, Brussels, 1979 September 1-3 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Center for Theoretical Studies, 1977-1980 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, 1982-1990 (Box 82, Folder 10-16)
- China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, 1990-1995 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  Restricted - Open in 2021.
- China Foundation for the Promotion of Education and Culture, 1976-1982 (Box 83, Folder 1-5)
- China Institute, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities (CICU), 1975-1978 (Box 83, Folder 7-9)
- Committee for an Effective UNESCO, 1975-1978 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Committee to Maintain a Prudent Defense Policy, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Commonwealth Fund Book Program Advisory Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 83, Folder 12-16)
- Commonwealth Fund Book Program Advisory Committee, 1986-1993 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
- COMTEX Scientific Corporation, 1982-1988 (Box 84, Folder 5-6)
- Conference Board, 1968-1973 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Congressional Action, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Consortium of Universities of Washington Metropolitan Area, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), 1969-1989 (Box 84, Folder 10-14)
- Council on Higher Education Institutions in New York City (CHEI), 1971-1975 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Committee on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD), 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Defense Science Board, 1970-1990 (Box 84, Folder 17-19)
- Defense Science Board - Task Force on Secrecy, 1969-1971 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Department of Defense, 1970-1979 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Department of Defense - Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1969-1971 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Department of Energy, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Department of State, 1971-1978 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Department of State - ECOSOC Committee on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD), 1973-1978 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Desert Research Institute, 1975-1984 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Charles Stark Draper Lab, 1974-1987 (Box 85, Folder 5-9)
- Dupont, 1969-1979 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- East Side Association, 1972-1976 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Federal Council for Science and Technology, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Finnish Academy of Science and Letters - Member, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Florida Institute of Technology - Senior Research Advisory Board, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Foreign Academies, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Franklin Institute, 1969-1986 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- French-American Foundation, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- General Motors Cancer Awards, 1978-1980 (Box 85, Folder 18-20)
- General Motors Cancer Awards, 1981-1992 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
- General Motors Research Laboratory, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- George Washington University - Institute for Technology and Strategic Research, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- George Washington University - 50th Anniversary of Announcement of Fission, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Gulf General Atomic, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1976-1981 (Box 86, Folder 7-16)
- John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1981-1990 (Box 87, Folder 1-5)
- Harcourt Brace Janovic, 1971-1981 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Harper and Row Publishers, 1968-1988 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Harvard University, 1969-1978 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Hertz Foundation Award (Fannie and John) (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Honeywell Award Committee, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Hudson Institute, 1975-1980 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Image Data Corporation, 1987-1991 (Box 87, Folder 12-13)
- Industrial Research, 1969-1973 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Institute for Defense Analyses, 1969-1977 (Box 87, Folder 15-20)
- Institute for Defense Analyses, 1977-1988 (Box 88, Folder 1-12)
- Institute for Educational Affairs, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Institute for the Future (IFF), 1968-1974 (Box 89, Folder 2-4)
- Institute for the Future (IFF) - Correspondence, 1969-1980 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, 1987-1989 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Institute for Health Policy Analysis, 1982-1990 (Box 89, Folder 7-11)
- Institut De La Vie, 1982-1986 (Box 89, Folder 12-17)
- Institut De La Vie, 1987-1992 (Box 90, Folder 1-8)
- Institut De La Vie, 1979-1981 (Box 90, Folder 9-10)
- Institute for Muscle Disease (IMD), 1971-1973 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Institute of Physics (London), 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- International Coordinating Group, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Institutional Association for Cultural Freedom, 1968-1974 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- International Association of Universities (IAU), 1970-1975 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), 1969-1979 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences (ICUS), 1975-1992 (Box 91, Folder 1-13)
- International Council for Educational Development (ICED), 1969-1975 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology (Belgium), 1975-1978 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- International Foundation for Science, 1978-1983 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- International Health Resource Consortium, 1977-1981 (Box 92, Folder 2-3)
- International Organization for the Study of Group Tensions, 1970-1992 (Box 92, Folder 4-5)
- International Parlimentary Group Advisory Board, 1984-1986 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- International Science Foundation - E. D. Haidemenakias, 1968-1974 (Box 92, Folder 7-8)
- International Space University, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- International Union of Pure and Applied Sciences (IUPAP), 1968-1981 (Box 92, Folder 10-16)
- Japan Institute of Metals, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Javits Committee on International Education and Cultural Exchange, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- Journal of College Science and Technology, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Lasker Foundation (Albert and Mary), 1969-1984 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- League of Women Voters, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 21)
- Leakey Foundation, 1979-1984 (Box 93, Folder 1-4)
- Library of Congress, 1971-1973 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Lieberman, David S. (Scientific papers) (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Link Foundation, 1982-1991 (Box 93, Folder 7-8)
- Seitz - Weekly Professional Appointment Calendars, 1968-1979 (Box 93)
- Texas Instruments, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 94, Folder 1-12)
- Texas Instruments, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 95, Folder 1-10)
- Texas Instruments - Callier Hearing and Speech Center, 1973-1976 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Texas Instruments - Founders Award, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Texas Instruments - Stock Ownership, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Akzona, Inc., 1972-1978 (Box 96, Folder 1-15)
- Akzona, Inc., 1978-1984 (Box 97, Folder 1-11)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD), 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 12-14)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD), 1978-1985 (Box 98, Folder 1-11)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD) - Chemrawn II, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD) - The Foundation for International Technological Cooperation, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- The Rockefeller University, Senate Meeting, 1969 December 16; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
  Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
- Senate Meeting, 1970 May 20; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Senate Meeting, February 10, Dr. Seitz, 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Views on Future Directions for The Rockefeller University, Discussion, Caspary Auditorium, 9:30-11am. Lecture - Dr. Jules Hirsch, Robert Shadley, Dr. James Hirsch, James Nagin, Dr. Merrill Chase, Richard Zigmond, 1970 June 12; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- 1969 National Academy of Sciences (NAS) Presentation of Academy Awards, April 28, 8pm, Great Hall, 1969 April 28; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Senate Meeting, 1970 November 17; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Senate Meeting, 2pm, Caspary Auditorium, 1970 June 1; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Senate Meeting, Pres. Seitz and Faculty, 4:30pm, Caspary Auditorium, 1969 October 1; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Concert Thomas Wagner, 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Senate Meeting, 4pm 204sl, 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- The Rockefeller University Convocation, 2-4pm, Caspary Auditorium, 1970 June 12; 2017:FA1069:001; Audio (Box 98)
- Senate Meeting, Caspary Auditorium, 2pm, 1970 June 4; Audio (Box 98)
- Pamphlets, Reprints and Biographical Data, 1950-1982 (Box 98, Folder 14-15)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD), 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD) - United Nations, 1976-1977 (Box 99, Folder 2-4)
- Council on Science and Technology for Development (CSTD) - State Department, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
- Science and Technology Advisory Group, NSF, 1975-1980 (Box 99, Folder 7-9)
- Science and Technology - Science Court, 1976-1977 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Science Service - General, 1969-1974 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Science Service - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Science Service - Committee on Development, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Academic Press, 1968-1973 (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
- United Aircraft Corporation, 1969-1971 (Box 100, Folder 3-4)
- United Aircraft Corporation - Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 October (Box 100, Folder 6)
- National Cancer Institute (NCI) - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB), 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 7-15)
- National Cancer Institute (NCI) - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB), 1972-1973, 1976-1976 (Box 101, Folder 1-15)
- National Cancer Institute (NCI) - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB), 1978 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- National Institutes of Health (NIH), 1978-1979 (Box 102, Folder 2-5)
- National Cancer Institute (NCI) - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB), 1979-1984 (Box 102, Folder 6-15)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - Outgoing - 1992 - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 1-5)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - Outgoing - 1993 - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 6-12)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - Outgoing - 1994 - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 13-19)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - Ougoing - 1974 - A-Z (Box 104)
  Closed - Preservation Concerns
- Seitz - Publications, 1964-1967 (Box 104)
- Rockefeller University Presidential Correspondence - Multiple Development, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
- Seitz - Affiliations, 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Research Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 6-8)
- Research Corporation - Minutes, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Research Corporation, 1975-1977 (Box 105, Folder 10-15)
- Research Corporation, 1978-1983 (Box 106, Folder 1-14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Minutes, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - General Information, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 2-4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Curriculum and Library Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Alumni Annual Giving, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - PSAC Personnel Security Forms (Box 107, Folder 8)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Pacific Science Center Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 107, Folder 9-10)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Alumni Annual Giving, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Board of Trustees General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Minutes - Board of Trustees General, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - General Information, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Nova University of Advanced Technology, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Nutrition Foundation - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 107, Folder 18-19)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Nutrition Foundation - General Information, 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Nutrition Foundation - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Nutrition Foundation, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - OAR Advisory Group, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - OAR Scientific Advisory Group, 1966-1967 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Oak Ridge Associated University - Monthly Highlights, Reports, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - OECD Contract, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corp., 1965-1967 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Planned Parenthood - World Population, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Minutes, 1969 January-May (Box 107, Folder 29)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 30)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Committee on Finance, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Honorary Degree Committee (Box 108, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Patterson Report, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Physics Department Advisory Council, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Committee on Plans and Resources, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Princeton - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Princeton, 1964, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 8-9)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Reference for Fellowships, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers -Puerto Rican Nuclear Center Contract, 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - PRNC, 1967-1969 (Box 108, Folder 12-14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Minutes, 1967, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 15-16)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Organization Study, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Rockefeller Foundation - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 18-19)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Rockefeller Foundation - General Information, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Rockefeller Foundation, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - NAS - General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - National Research Council (Box 108, Folder 24)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - National Security Industrial Association (Seitz), 1967 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - NAS - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - NAS - General, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - NAS - General, 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 28-29)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - NAS - Minutes, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 30)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Rockefeller University (Seitz) (Box 108, Folder 31)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Naval Research Advisory Committee - General, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 32)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Nova University (Seitz), 1968 (Box 108, Folder 33)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - National Research Council - Minutes and Draft Notes, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - National Citizens Committee to Save Education and Library Funds, 1969-1970 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - State Governments - Illinois Science Advisory Council - General, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - State Governments - Illinois Science Advisory Council - Meetings, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Illinois - Science Advisory Council Report, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - State Governments - Illinois Science Advisory Council - Meetings, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - State Governments - Illinois Science Advisory Council - General, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - State Governments - Illinois Science Advisory Council, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Personal (Seitz) - Franklin Institute - Franklin Medal Award, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Graduate Research Center of the Southwest (Seitz), 1966 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 11)